welcome to another installment of spring
欢迎来到春季的另一期
tips this is actually a very special
提示这实际上是很特别的
extra installment of spring tips for the
额外安装的弹簧头
season in light of the amazing
鉴于惊人的季节
revelations from last week's epic spring
上周史诗般的春天的启示
one platform event in this installment
本期中的一个平台事件
we're going to take a very brief look at
我们将简要介绍一下
banners and their place in the spring
横幅及其在春天的位置
boot application so we're gonna go ahead
启动应用程序，所以我们要继续
and use two dados snapshot the latest
并使用两个最新的dados快照
and greatest we're not using tonight oh
最棒的是我们今晚不使用哦
final yeah because it's not here yet
是的，因为还没有来
now we're not gonna use m7 because the
现在我们不使用m7，因为
feature doesn't exist in that release so
该功能在该版本中不存在，因此
we'll go ahead and just leave it as is
我们将继续进行，并保持原样
hit demo and that'll give us a zip file
点击演示，这会给我们一个zip文件
we'll go here we have the the project as
我们去这里，我们有项目
usual we're gonna open this up in our
通常我们会在我们的
IDE and we have as I saying absolutely
IDE和我们完全一样
nothing on the classpath we have no no
类路径上没有任何内容，我们没有，没有
web support node APA nothing but it's
Web支持节点APA，仅此而已
still a Springwood application and a
仍然是Springwood应用程序和
spring bit application with nothing on
弹簧位应用程序，什么都没有
it can still start and that really is
它仍然可以开始，那确实是
all we need in this case right for our
在这种情况下，我们需要的只是适合我们的
simple demo so let's go ahead and open
简单的演示，让我们继续打开
up the class here the main entry point
在这里上课的主要切入点
into the application and kick it off
进入应用程序并开始
run off shift
倒班
ten
十
okay
好的
all right so there we are we have the
好的，所以我们到了
aplia application it's up and running
Aplia应用程序已启动并正在运行
this ask at work has been in spring boot
这个工作上的要求一直在 spring boot
in some form another since the first you
从第一个你开始
know the very first releases this ask
知道这个问题的第一个版本
get work used to be black and white only
以前只能从事黑白工作
right and it's a it's become a much
对，这是一个很大的
beloved feature of spring boot I think
我认为弹簧靴的最受欢迎功能
people all around the world would agree
世界各地的人们都会同意
that it's being good is better for this
很好对这个更好
ASCII art work I personally have always
我个人一直有的ASCII艺术作品
been a fan and for this reason that I
一直是粉丝，因此我
want to take a brief digression and talk
想简短地讨论一下
about what I consider to be very serious
关于我认为非常认真的
to deficiency and IntelliJ Japan's
不足和IntelliJ Japan的
product for while I'm a fan I never
我永远不会成为粉丝的产品
really understood why this was here so
真的知道为什么在这里
if you go to edit configurations you can
如果您要编辑配置，则可以
see it says hide banner to me that's a
看到它对我说隐藏横幅
very dumb feature I don't know why they
非常笨拙的功能，我不知道为什么
have even there I think we should get
我想我们甚至应该在那里
rid of it so I did what all of us would
摆脱它，所以我做了我们所有人都会做的
have done in that same position I went
在我去过的相同位置做过
on the internet and I complained and
在互联网上，我抱怨和
cried on the internet right so I sent
在互联网上哭了，所以我发送了
out a message on Twitter and I
在Twitter和我上留言
complained and my friend Jana branya
抱怨和我的朋友贾娜·布兰妮亚
branya is a software developer let's see
branya是一个软件开发人员，让我们来看看
he's a software developer by passion and
他是一位热情满满的软件开发人员，
IntelliJ IDEA Japan's he responded with
IntelliJ IDEA Japan的回应
a message of hope which I share with you
我与您分享希望的信息
here now right so we can see clearly
现在在这里，所以我们可以清楚地看到
there's hope on the horizon things are
在地平线上有希望
gonna be fine hope springs eternal so
美好的希望会永恒
that said the the the banner is really
那个横幅真的是
really compelling there are options for
真正令人信服的是
the banner itself you can actually
横幅本身，您实际上可以
change the banner you can say a banner
更改横幅您可以说横幅
dot there you go what kind of banner
点到那里你去什么样的横幅
don't want to want it to run on the
不想让它在
console with system that out or don't
带有或不带系统的控制台
want it to be logged right if I did this
希望我这样做时将其正确记录
for example you would actually get the
例如，您实际上会得到
same application so it's the old okay
相同的应用程序，这是旧的
right so it's there we go it's a
对，所以就在那里，我们去了
actually part of a log now as opposed to
现在实际上是日志的一部分，而不是
them as opposed in the console I think
他们认为与控制台相反
that should be you know I think it's
那应该是你知道的我认为是
fine as it as it was whatever you do do
就像您所做的一切一样好
not put off that's a terrible option
不推迟那是一个糟糕的选择
just hit console right so there we go
只需点击控制台就可以了
furnace again back to where we were okay
再次回到我们没事的地方
so that's that's the default behavior
这就是默认行为
now it's worth noting that in the first
现在值得注意的是
versions we didn't support color codes
我们不支持颜色代码的版本
all right this this is a new feature
好吧，这是一个新功能
that came in and I don't know 1.2 1.3
进来了，我不知道1.2 1.3
and the code of codes are very important
而且代码的代码非常重要
addition they they make it so that you
另外他们做到了，所以你
can do a lot of very interesting things
可以做很多非常有趣的事情
so you can change the the Asguard as
因此您可以将Asguard更改为
well that's the important bit here right
好吧，这是重要的一点
it's got it supports color codes and it
它支持颜色代码，并且
supports customization so let's first
支持自定义，所以我们先
look at customization I'll run my little
看定制，我会尽我所能
program here CD desktop and I've got
程序在这里CD桌面，我有
banners dot py the first one okay so now
横幅点py第一个好吧，现在
if you look at this I've got to bend it
如果你看这个，我得弯腰
out txt file here and this just says
txt文件在这里，这只是说
spring tips right it's just the so I
春天的提示对，就是这样
just went to an online a skewer
刚去网上一串
generator and they're just a bunch of
发电机，它们只是一堆
them in 4/4 axed ASCII text generators
在4/4的ASCII文本生成器中使用它们
right yes CII
是的，CII
ASCII so now if we run this again you
ASCII，所以现在如果我们再次运行它
can see the application reflects our
可以看到应用程序反映了我们的
customized spring tips ASCII banner
定制的弹簧提示ASCII标语
right so that's that's one way to change
对，那是改变的一种方式
the behavior of the application another
应用程序的行为
as I say is to use color codes so let's
我说的是使用颜色代码，所以让我们
now do the second one and now we've got
现在做第二个，现在我们有了
a different a security and you can see
不同的证券，您可以看到
that here we're using color codes and
在这里我们使用颜色代码
there's actually these little symbols
实际上有这些小符号
that are good that'll be replaced for
将会被取代的好东西
you by spring boot and to cut our black
你的 spring boot 和削减我们的黑色
into color bright red black etcetera so
变成彩色鲜红色黑色等
whatever you put here is then cut in or
放在这里的任何东西都切入或
whatever you put after these color codes
这些颜色代码后面的内容
is colorized by the code that precedes
由前面的代码着色
it right so the first these characters
对，所以第一个这些字符
are gonna be blue those are the red
会是蓝色的那些是红色的
yellow etcetera so let's see what that
黄色等，让我们看看
gives us right I think you can agree
给我们权利，我想你可以同意
that's pretty darned awesome so we have
这真是太棒了，所以我们有
now color ask yard
现在颜色问码
I'm a fan but this is not they not not
我是粉丝，但这不是他们不是
they final you know stretches out the
他们最终知道延伸
final feature by any means we on the
最终功能，无论如何我们
spring blue team don't rest on our
春季蓝队不要依赖我们
laurels so in a in 2015
月桂树在2015年
one of the most arguably one of the most
最有争议的之一
memorable powerful features ever added
令人难忘的强大功能
to spring boot was Sena it was submitted
spring boot 是塞纳（Sena），它已提交
this is a ski our banner generated from
这是我们的横幅生成的滑雪板
an image this is submitted by Craig
这是Craig提交的图片
Burke who send it with some devil you
伯克带着魔鬼送给你
know some default properties and sent
知道一些默认属性并发送
along some suggested artwork right so
以及一些建议的艺术品吧
this you know here's an example of
你知道这是一个例子
spring boot co-founder Phil web as a ski
Spring Boot联合创始人Phil Web作为滑雪者
at work in the first pull request this
在工作中的第一个请求
is November 30 2015 so you know two
是2015年11月30日，所以您知道两个
years ago and this took a long time to
年前，这花了很长时间
get right this is arguably the most
说对了，这可以说是最
important feature we've ever added if
我们曾经添加过的重要功能
you look here people said that this is
你看这里人们说这是
the last thing stopping our team from
最后一件事阻止我们的团队
adopting spring would everywhere
春季到处都会
any chance of back porting it to 1.2 and
任何将其移植回1.2的机会，
then Craig Burke who was the author of
然后是克雷格·伯克（Craig Burke），他是《
the pull request in the first place he
首先是拉取请求
says I'm shutting down all my current
说我要关闭我所有的电流
Supreme Buddha applications in
至尊佛陀在
production until this is merged I'll
生产，直到合并为止
probably get fired but this is important
可能会被解雇，但这很重要
and I need to stand on principle here
我需要在这里坚持原则
and of course a fill web response
当然还有填充网络响应
spring boot went up three has been out
spring boot 上升了三已经出
for weeks now weeks what are you still
现在几周了你还剩下什么
doing on 1.2 other people said that
对其他1.2个人说
other technologies like Rat Pack which
其他技术，例如Rat Pack
is a fairly new project have supported
是否支持一个相当新的项目
for a long time this this person says
很长一段时间，这个人说
I'm pretty sure Rat Pack has supported
我很确定Rat Pack支持
this for five to six years why spring
这五到六年为什么春天
stuck in the dark ages
卡在黑暗时代
dan wood who works in the Rat Pack
在Rat Pack中工作的Dan Wood
project is I can confirm Rat Pack is
项目是我可以确认Rat Pack是
supported it's for six point five years
支持了五年六点
spring boot more like enterprise release
spring boot 更像企业发布
cycle boot and then of course Phil
循环启动，然后当然是Phil
responds such an unfair comparison Rat
回应这样不公平的比较
Pack is asynchronous and unblocking and
包是异步的并且是无阻塞的
as a result they can do everything
结果，他们可以做所有事情
faster I think we need to consider the
更快，我认为我们需要考虑
bigger picture here and look at how we
这里更大的图片，看看我们如何
can work together to create a standard
可以共同创建一个标准
Craig would you be able to drop the
克雷格，您能丢下
specification and create a TCK I'm happy
规范并创建一个TCK我很高兴
to donate avatar to the project and I
为项目捐赠头像，我
believe that this would make a fine
相信这会很好
default banner for all projects I also
我也是所有项目的默认横幅
forgot we're going to need the weights
忘了我们将需要重量
but I need a way to specify banners in
但我需要一种方法来指定横幅
XML to which of course Craig responds
XML当然是Craig响应的
draft a specification created ttk xml
起草一个创建的ttk xml规范
banners what would that look like what
横幅看起来像什么
let me know what you need that can work
让我知道您需要的东西可以工作
on it Phil IRB's response I'm imagining
我想像的是Phil IRB的回应
some sort of cross between doc book and
文档书和
wisdom and then of course Andy Wilkinson
智慧，当然还有安迪·威尔金森
also on the Springwood team responds
也在斯普林伍德队回应
well if we're gonna go with XML we ought
好吧，如果我们要使用XML，我们应该
to ensure it's as concise as possible
确保它尽可能简洁
a single pixel banner is only 16 lines
单个像素横幅只有16行
of XML look at that that's glorious and
XML的角度来看那是光荣的，
that and then Craig responds this all
那然后克雷格回应了这一切
seems very reasonable I'll have it done
看起来很合理，我会解决的
within the hour and it goes on it gets a
在一个小时之内，它会继续
little it gets a little crazy at some
有点疯狂
point Craig just responds I'm just gonna
点克雷格只是回应我会
throw the banner in to see data it's
扔横幅以查看它的数据
valid XML that's all I really care about
我真正关心的是有效的XML
people go back and forth on the
人们来回走
technical you know in dynamics of the of
您了解动态的技术
the future and then finally December 2
未来，最后是12月2日
and now a few days later Phil Phil web
现在几天后，Phil Phil网站
responds I'm afraid the results of the
回应，恐怕结果
discussion was to merge this and 1.4 we
讨论是将这个和1.4我们合并
considered 1.3 but when you decided that
考虑1.3，但当你决定
without a killer why not for feature
没有杀手级的功能
people just won't upgrade to good to H
人们只是不会升级到H
Greg responds sir Craig responds I
格雷格回应克雷格先生回应我
certainly hope your gamble pays off and
希望您的赌注能得到回报，
then in light of that people have you
然后鉴于有人拥有你
know some ideas about color models and
知道一些有关颜色模型的想法，
you know how to get all the color codes
你知道如何获得所有颜色代码
correct and then of course people like
正确，然后人们当然喜欢
Seabourn a here created a image to
Seabourn在这里创建了一个图像
spring but-- banner that uses that that
春天，但是-使用那个的横幅
software to create your own banner and
创建自己的横幅的软件，以及
of course craig responds back that's
当然，克雷格回信那是
great i did they I had the same idea and
太好了，我做到了，我有相同的想法，
I built a command-line utility here this
我在这里建立了一个命令行工具
is again December 11th 2015
又是2015年12月11日
it's a command-line utility you can cat
这是您可以使用的命令行实用程序
an image to it and it'll turn into ASCII
图像，它会变成ASCII
art work there I also built a REST API a
在那里我还建立了一个REST API
spring boot REST API that you could curl
可以卷曲的Spring Boot REST API
images to and then you know I'm putting
图像到然后你知道我在放
images too and it would it would dump
图像也将它转储
out the ASCII art representation of that
的ASCII艺术表示
image the source code of course is a
图片的源代码当然是
patch to license and it's available here
补丁程序许可，可在此处获得
and just long beautiful banners people
还有长久美丽的横幅人
went back and forth I think Craig
我想克雷格来回
responds has anyone ever done anything
回应有没有人做过任何事情
something kind of dumb and then things
有点愚蠢，然后事情
kind of snowball and get out of hand
像滚雪球一样，一发不可收拾
and you don't know how to stop it no me
你不知道该如何制止
either and then Matt rebels Matt ratable
要么然后马特叛军马特
of course is why would you stop it and
当然是为什么您要停止它，并且
people went on and on and then somebody
人们继续前进，然后有人
else built an adder and you know an
否则建立一个加法器，你知道
image to banner feature as well and then
图像到横幅功能，然后
more people built it on top of that
越来越多的人在此基础上构建它
here's a swagger version of it right -
这是它的醒目的版本-
using my code that and my project with a
使用我的代码和我的项目
simple UI and then people went on and on
简单的用户界面，然后人们继续
and on and of course we got to a point
然后我们当然到了
where eventually eventually April 8 2016
最终最终于2016年4月8日
this feature was added to
此功能已添加到
you know the the actual code base in its
你知道它的实际代码库
merged try this is this this is what
合并尝试这就是这个
Phil Webb said at the time this is now
菲尔·韦伯（Phil Webb）当时说现在
merged thanks for one of the most
合并最感谢之一
important pull requests in the history
历史上重要的请求请求
of the project and of course at the time
该项目，当然在当时
this inspired a whole avalanche of
这激发了整个雪崩
amazing you know demos from the
令人惊讶的是您知道演示
community so if you go here you can
社区，所以如果你去这里就可以
search for tweet boot banner and there's
搜索推特启动横幅，并有
a number of great boot banners that came
出现了许多很棒的启动标语
out of this right so here's spring batch
在这个权利之外，这是春季批
lead michael t manila responding with
带领迈克尔·t·马尼拉回应
the character of dennis rodman here's a
丹尼斯·罗德曼（Dennis Rodman）的角色是
craig burke that's much better looking
克雷格·伯克，看起来更好
at oh that's a control if I've ever seen
在哦，如果我见过，那是一个控制
it
它
i dieter who bow responds with this you
我节食的人鞠躬回应了你
know that dog pointing at you as a tweet
知道那只狗把你指着是一条推文
as a boot banner here's Phil web showing
作为启动横幅，这是Phil网站上显示的内容
a photo of Margaret Hamilton standing
玛格丽特·汉密尔顿站立的照片
next to the code that she wrote to take
在她编写的代码旁边
NASA to the moon using the stream blue
美国国家航空航天局使用流蓝色到月球
banner the the Saarland jug responds to
萨尔州水罐响应横幅
our Duke as a spring boot banner and a
我们的公爵作为 spring boot 的旗帜和
Wilkinson of course didn't quite get the
威尔金森当然不是很了解
idea but we'll give him will give him a
想法，但我们会给他的，会给他一个
pass
通过
Matt Slater you know mentioned me and
你知道马特·斯莱特（Matt Slater）提到我
says make chart at war and there's they
说在战争中制作图表，有
asked at work there at him ed who
问他在工作地点
Melinda's community member and legend
梅琳达的社区成员和传奇
Eddie Melendez responds with the my
埃迪·梅伦德斯（Eddie Melendez）以我的回应
Venus logo as Twitter boot banner the
金星徽标作为Twitter启动横幅
seaman Bosley at the time a Couchbase
当时的海员Bosley Couchbase
showed a photo of a boot plus character
展示了一张靴子加人物的照片
face logo equals heart that's awesome
脸部徽标等于超赞的心
kubernetes there's the web responding to
kubernetes有网络响应
me saying mister starbucks man spring
我说星巴克先生春天
developer advocate an all-around nice
开发者提倡全方位的好
guy that's a photo of me I guess and
我猜是我的照片的家伙
there's Stephanie Cole and Michael
有斯蒂芬妮·科尔和迈克尔
Simmons community members and and so on
Simmons社区成员等
of a tip about the image banner here's
关于图像横幅的提示的是
the you know boot banner from my table
你知道我桌上的启动横幅
showing J hipster right J hipster logo
向右显示J时髦J时髦徽标
spring gotta lead Oliver Gurkha responds
春天必须带领奥利弗·古尔卡回应
with the photo of a boot with some
与一些靴子的照片
spring Leafs coming out of it awesome
春天的叶子令人赞叹不已
right here's the the Utah the delicate
就在犹他州
arch in Utah here's the Gopher from
犹他州的拱门这里是地鼠
golang in spring boot from toshiaki
从toshiaki spring boot golang
monkey and our community legend and in
猴子和我们的社区传奇
the Tokyo area the spring cloud dataflow
东京地区春季云数据流
logo you know updated with their the
您知道的徽标已更新为
Sasuke artwork
佐助的艺术品
more stuff I don't quite understand what
更多的东西，我不太明白
this one says obviously I don't read
这个说显然我不读
Japanese but some some suggestions from
日语，但有一些建议
from Japan who's the Japan Japanese Java
来自日本的日本日语Java
user group as etc dr. Saigon even got in
用户组等西贡甚至进去了
and on the joke and showed us their
开个玩笑，向我们展示了他们的
their banner for their tool which isn't
他们工具的标语不是
spring poop but it's so pretty cool
春天的大便，但它非常酷
we got this one oh it does the robot
我们得到了这个哦，它做了机器人
from Star Wars right and then of course
当然是从《星球大战》开始的
we've got Putin and Yoda and you know it
我们有普京和尤达，你知道吗
goes on right there's just a number of
继续下去，只有一些
different things out there number
不同的东西在那里号码
different banners out there there's
那里有不同的横幅
Kafka of course Cassandra you know I'm
卡夫卡当然是卡桑德拉，你知道我
not sure where that is it looks like a
不知道那是哪里
stormtrooper or some sort what is that
突击队员或某种什么
oh go code troopers okay that makes
哦，去吧，代码突击队
sense right lots of different different
感觉正确很多不同
apps options out there and here's of
应用程序选项在那里，这里的
course the you know the the epic
当然你知道史诗
conclusion of all that the spring Doge
春天总督的结论
in a scare works so lots of great stuff
在恐慌中有很多很棒的东西
and I and that's why you know it's
我，这就是为什么你知道
useful to look at what this gives us
看看这给我们带来了什么
this is the and the color mascara we can
这是和我们可以的颜色睫毛膏
also do better we can use images so
也可以做得更好我们可以使用图像
let's do that that's a three and it's my
让我们做到那是三个，这是我的
third one so now well run the
第三，所以现在运行良好
application here CD downloads demo may
此处的应用程序CD下载演示可能
even spring - boot run I'll to clean all
即使是春季-开机运行，我都会清理所有
right look at that so there is a spring
正确的看那有一个春天
logo that's an image alright if you look
徽标，如果您看的话，图像就可以了
at whatever what I've got in the
无论我有什么
directory here I've got been it up PNG
目录我在这里PNG
that's this thing right here and I got
这就是这个东西，我得到了
turned into the spring leaf in a scared
在恐惧中变成春天的叶子
that's awesome so there we go that's you
那太棒了，我们去那就是你
know I didn't have to do anything to get
知道我不需要做任何事情
that that just works that's that's a the
那是可行的，那是一个
image feature and that's you know really
图像功能，这就是您真正知道的
the state of the art has remained since
从那以后一直保持着最先进的状态
one that for now and spring one platform
现在就推出一个平台
2017 just last week during the first day
2017年刚好在第一天
keynote we revealed the biggest and best
主题演讲，我们揭示了最大和最好的
feature ever and I'll show it to you now
曾经有特色，我现在将向您展示
okay so desktop banners pew I
好吧，所以桌面标语我
and I think it's four okay and now look
我认为现在还可以四点
at that animated banners boys there's
在那些动画横幅男孩那里
music playing I hear music I hear epic
音乐播放我听到音乐我听到史诗
music in my head watching this now sure
我脑海里的音乐现在肯定在看
it adds like 30 seconds to the startup
它增加了大约30秒的启动时间
time I don't even care that's so great
时间我什至不在乎那太好了
that's awesome so when we showed this
太棒了，所以当我们展示这个
there's a you know oysters trying to
有一个你知道牡蛎试图
applause the entire auditorium went
鼓掌整个礼堂
crazy and I I said we should have just
疯了，我说我们应该
shut down the conference then and there
然后在那里关掉会议
there's no point in continuing
没有继续的意义
we had animated s camera so that my
我们有动画相机，所以我的
friends is the future I hope you'll
朋友是未来，我希望你会
consider that when you build your next
在构建下一个时要考虑
Springwood application or you know why
Springwood应用程序或您知道为什么
not revisit your ones if you you know if
如果您知道的话，不要重访您的
you're not already planning on going to
您还没有计划去
spring glue to that oh this should be a
弹簧胶，哦，这应该是
compelling enough reason to justify the
充分的理由来证明
upgrade so you know get to get on it
升级，所以您可以继续前进
animated your your banners and with that
动画您的横幅，并以此
thanks so much for watching and we'll
非常感谢您的收看，我们会
see you next time
下次见
you
您